[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Jeremy, how has business been in this gun store since the Sandy Hook massacre?", "question_tokens": ["Jeremy", ",", "how", "has", "business", "been", "in", "this", "gun", "store", "since", "the", "Sandy", "Hook", "massacre", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "We've increased our sales four to five times.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "increased", "our", "sales", "four", "to", "five", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "Why are people reacting to such an appalling massacre are raising out to buy more guns and ammunition?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "people", "reacting", "to", "such", "an", "appalling", "massacre", "are", "raising", "out", "to", "buy", "more", "guns", "and", "ammunition", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "So I can't speak for any other state but Texas.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "I", "ca", "n't", "speak", "for", "any", "other", "state", "but", "Texas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "For self-defense for your home or self-defense of your property?", "question_tokens": ["For", "self-defense", "for", "your", "home", "or", "self-defense", "of", "your", "property", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Your home.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Do you believe any guns should be banned?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "any", "guns", "should", "be", "banned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "I do not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "It's not guns that kill people.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "guns", "that", "kill", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "But do you believe that the more guns there are in America the safer the country is?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "believe", "that", "the", "more", "guns", "there", "are", "in", "America", "the", "safer", "the", "country", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "In the hands of the right people, yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "hands", "of", "the", "right", "people", ",", "yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["15"], "ORGANIZATION": ["JP Enterprises"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "And what are we going to start with?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "are", "we", "going", "to", "start", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Let's start with the JP Enterprises, semiautomatic, AR- 15.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "start", "with", "the", "JP", "Enterprises", ",", "semiautomatic", ",", "AR-", "15", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "And this is the pure unmodified semiautomatic?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "is", "the", "pure", "unmodified", "semiautomatic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "I have to try to flip it into an automatic?", "question_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "try", "to", "flip", "it", "into", "an", "automatic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "It's a bog standard, if you like, AR-15?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "bog", "standard", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "AR-15", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "-NONE-", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "And that's perfectly legal?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "perfectly", "legal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "So all of this is perfectly legal to any American who is not a felon or has a history of mental illness?", "question_tokens": ["So", "all", "of", "this", "is", "perfectly", "legal", "to", "any", "American", "who", "is", "not", "a", "felon", "or", "has", "a", "history", "of", "mental", "illness", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Somebody who knows really what they're doing, how many rounds could they fire in, say, a minute with one of these?", "question_tokens": ["Somebody", "who", "knows", "really", "what", "they", "'re", "doing", ",", "how", "many", "rounds", "could", "they", "fire", "in", ",", "say", ",", "a", "minute", "with", "one", "of", "these", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, you know, with reload, maybe 60 rounds or so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "with", "reload", ",", "maybe", "60", "rounds", "or", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Sorry?", "question_tokens": ["Sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "LCEDE: The -- the true cyclical rate if you had unlimited magazine, then it could shoot about 400 rounds a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["LCEDE", ":", "The", "--", "the", "true", "cyclical", "rate", "if", "you", "had", "unlimited", "magazine", ",", "then", "it", "could", "shoot", "about", "400", "rounds", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Two hundred?", "question_tokens": ["Two", "hundred", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "If I had to guess.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "had", "to", "guess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Do you think that's a good idea?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "For law-abiding citizens, I think it's an excellent idea.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "law-abiding", "citizens", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "an", "excellent", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "And that's the only difference?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "the", "only", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "That's the only difference.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "only", "difference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "How sophisticated is it -- I mean, how difficult is it for somebody who knows what they're doing to take an AR-15 and make it like an automatic?", "question_tokens": ["How", "sophisticated", "is", "it", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "how", "difficult", "is", "it", "for", "somebody", "who", "knows", "what", "they", "'re", "doing", "to", "take", "an", "AR-15", "and", "make", "it", "like", "an", "automatic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Well, you have to have drill well the inside of a receiver, of course you have to have the right receive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "to", "have", "drill", "well", "the", "inside", "of", "a", "receiver", ",", "of", "course", "you", "have", "to", "have", "the", "right", "receive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "But the parts can be bought legally?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "parts", "can", "be", "bought", "legally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Yes, they can.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "they", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "You could buy them separately?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "buy", "them", "separately", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "You can.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "But if you're in a confined area like a movie theater, you don't really care, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "'re", "in", "a", "confined", "area", "like", "a", "movie", "theater", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "really", "care", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Well, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "And the guy -- the guy at Aurora used an AR-15 and I think he had what's called a slider device?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "guy", "--", "the", "guy", "at", "Aurora", "used", "an", "AR-15", "and", "I", "think", "he", "had", "what", "'s", "called", "a", "slider", "device", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "LCEDE: Slide Fire Stock.", "answer_tokens": ["LCEDE", ":", "Slide", "Fire", "Stock", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What does that do to an AR-15?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "do", "to", "an", "AR-15", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "It allows the weapon -- it's even less accurate than this and it's really hard to actually shoot.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "allows", "the", "weapon", "--", "it", "'s", "even", "less", "accurate", "than", "this", "and", "it", "'s", "really", "hard", "to", "actually", "shoot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "How many bullets does it allow you to fire?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "bullets", "does", "it", "allow", "you", "to", "fire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Well, technically it shoots about 650 rounds a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "technically", "it", "shoots", "about", "650", "rounds", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "And you sell them here?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "sell", "them", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Of all the arguments to have one of these, home defense is probably the least plausible from your point of view?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "arguments", "to", "have", "one", "of", "these", ",", "home", "defense", "is", "probably", "the", "least", "plausible", "from", "your", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "For me in the home, what people are talking about is, you know, the way this world is going that the military and United Nations are going to come in and try to take our guns.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "me", "in", "the", "home", ",", "what", "people", "are", "talking", "about", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "way", "this", "world", "is", "going", "that", "the", "military", "and", "United", "Nations", "are", "going", "to", "come", "in", "and", "try", "to", "take", "our", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Do you really believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Can you imagine U.S. Marines charging on to your property and try to steal your guns?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "imagine", "U.S.", "Marines", "charging", "on", "to", "your", "property", "and", "try", "to", "steal", "your", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "I would hope not, but if it's an executive order --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "hope", "not", ",", "but", "if", "it", "'s", "an", "executive", "order", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "But do you think the American military would attack its own people?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "the", "American", "military", "would", "attack", "its", "own", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "If they're forced to.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "they", "'re", "forced", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "And do you think that's what many Texans feel about why they would need a weapon like this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "what", "many", "Texans", "feel", "about", "why", "they", "would", "need", "a", "weapon", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "WP", "JJ", "NNPS", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "They want it because they are law-abiding citizens and they know it's legal to purchase it now and it won't be legal later.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "want", "it", "because", "they", "are", "law-abiding", "citizens", "and", "they", "know", "it", "'s", "legal", "to", "purchase", "it", "now", "and", "it", "wo", "n't", "be", "legal", "later", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Easy to use?", "question_tokens": ["Easy", "to", "use", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$25,000", "$45,000"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "$", "CD", "TO", "$", "CD", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "What will it cost me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "it", "cost", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "These run anywhere from $25,000 to $45,000, depends on the make and model.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "run", "anywhere", "from", "$", "25,000", "to", "$", "45,000", ",", "depends", "on", "the", "make", "and", "model", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "What is the rate of fire of one of these?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "rate", "of", "fire", "of", "one", "of", "these", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "It's about 900 rounds a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "900", "rounds", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "You sit like this.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "sit", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Why would any civilian want -- need one of these?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "any", "civilian", "want", "--", "need", "one", "of", "these", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "This is an investment.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "an", "investment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "I could buy that from you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "could", "buy", "that", "from", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "You could.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What was your reaction to what he said?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "what", "he", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, it seems to be more show than reality because it seems like on the very same day the majority leader came out and said that they're not going to pass any assault weapons ban.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "seems", "to", "be", "more", "show", "than", "reality", "because", "it", "seems", "like", "on", "the", "very", "same", "day", "the", "majority", "leader", "came", "out", "and", "said", "that", "they", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "pass", "any", "assault", "weapons", "ban", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Do you support 100 percent background checks -- universal background checks?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "support", "100", "percent", "background", "checks", "--", "universal", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ":", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "No, the problem that we have with regard to the background checks is that current background checks are not working.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "the", "problem", "that", "we", "have", "with", "regard", "to", "the", "background", "checks", "is", "that", "current", "background", "checks", "are", "not", "working", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "In principle -- in principle of universal background checks, do you support that?", "question_tokens": ["In", "principle", "--", "in", "principle", "of", "universal", "background", "checks", ",", "do", "you", "support", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, the principle of ensuring that criminals and those who have mental issues do not get their hands on guns are very important.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "principle", "of", "ensuring", "that", "criminals", "and", "those", "who", "have", "mental", "issues", "do", "not", "get", "their", "hands", "on", "guns", "are", "very", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Can you guarantee that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "guarantee", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "What we need to do is enforce the laws and take measures to crack down on violence, to help those with mental challenges, to put the criminals behind bars and prevent criminals from getting a hold of guns in the first place.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "we", "need", "to", "do", "is", "enforce", "the", "laws", "and", "take", "measures", "to", "crack", "down", "on", "violence", ",", "to", "help", "those", "with", "mental", "challenges", ",", "to", "put", "the", "criminals", "behind", "bars", "and", "prevent", "criminals", "from", "getting", "a", "hold", "of", "guns", "in", "the", "first", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Would you support a ban on magazines that have more than 10 rounds?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "support", "a", "ban", "on", "magazines", "that", "have", "more", "than", "10", "rounds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Because look at the Texas border itself.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "look", "at", "the", "Texas", "border", "itself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "But has any Texas rancher, to your knowledge, ever been confronted with a Mexican drug cartel?", "question_tokens": ["But", "has", "any", "Texas", "rancher", ",", "to", "your", "knowledge", ",", "ever", "been", "confronted", "with", "a", "Mexican", "drug", "cartel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 323, "question": "When?", "question_tokens": ["When", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Every month you'll have --", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "month", "you", "'ll", "have", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "With Mexican drug cartels and Texan farmers?", "question_tokens": ["With", "Mexican", "drug", "cartels", "and", "Texan", "farmers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Do you agree with the fact that you can't legally buy, in most places in America, machine guns, you know, warfare style machine guns?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "ca", "n't", "legally", "buy", ",", "in", "most", "places", "in", "America", ",", "machine", "guns", ",", "you", "know", ",", "warfare", "style", "machine", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Do you support that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "support", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Well, that's a ban that's in place.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "ban", "that", "'s", "in", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Do you support it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "support", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "We have been fined with that ban.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "been", "fined", "with", "that", "ban", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":"], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "However --", "answer_tokens": ["However", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Why do you -- why doesn't that breach your constitutional rights?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "--", "why", "does", "n't", "that", "breach", "your", "constitutional", "rights", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "What is your definition of an assault rifle, given I can legally buy that here and kill 300 people in one minute?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "definition", "of", "an", "assault", "rifle", ",", "given", "I", "can", "legally", "buy", "that", "here", "and", "kill", "300", "people", "in", "one", "minute", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Well, first, I think that any Texan has a right to be able to purchase one of those weapons.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "I", "think", "that", "any", "Texan", "has", "a", "right", "to", "be", "able", "to", "purchase", "one", "of", "those", "weapons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "What did you feel when you heard about this in terms of what Chris was trying to achieve?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "heard", "about", "this", "in", "terms", "of", "what", "Chris", "was", "trying", "to", "achieve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I didn't -- I still -- I guess I'm still in total disbelief that Chris is gone.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "--", "I", "still", "--", "I", "guess", "I", "'m", "still", "in", "total", "disbelief", "that", "Chris", "is", "gone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "But against what?", "question_tokens": ["But", "against", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Against a lot of things.", "answer_tokens": ["Against", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "The guy who put a gun to my head -- have you ever had a gun to your head?", "question_tokens": ["The", "guy", "who", "put", "a", "gun", "to", "my", "head", "--", "have", "you", "ever", "had", "a", "gun", "to", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Have you ever had a man look you in the eyes and say I'm going to blow your head off?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "had", "a", "man", "look", "you", "in", "the", "eyes", "and", "say", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "blow", "your", "head", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Why would you have needed an AR-15 in that situation?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "have", "needed", "an", "AR-15", "in", "that", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "You're missing the point of what I'm saying.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "missing", "the", "point", "of", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Do you fear tyranny, genuinely?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fear", "tyranny", ",", "genuinely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "No, I don't fear tyranny.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "fear", "tyranny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Were they looting?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "they", "looting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "It was limited looting.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "limited", "looting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "What is your answer to the parents of Sandy Hook who had their children blown to pieces about how you are personally, through the instrument of your radio show, going to try and make America a safer place than it was?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "answer", "to", "the", "parents", "of", "Sandy", "Hook", "who", "had", "their", "children", "blown", "to", "pieces", "about", "how", "you", "are", "personally", ",", "through", "the", "instrument", "of", "your", "radio", "show", ",", "going", "to", "try", "and", "make", "America", "a", "safer", "place", "than", "it", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Simple.", "answer_tokens": ["Simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Armed teachers or armed guards?", "question_tokens": ["Armed", "teachers", "or", "armed", "guards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "CC", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Either one.", "answer_tokens": ["Either", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA", "NRA"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Do you believe the NRA agrees with this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "the", "NRA", "agrees", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Do I believe that the NRA agrees with -- I don't know what the NRA agrees with me or not.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "I", "believe", "that", "the", "NRA", "agrees", "with", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "NRA", "agrees", "with", "me", "or", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Am I wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "It worked out.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "worked", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "What did we change?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "we", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "You have actually people in your country that decided long ago that they didn't want to have one man over an entire nation.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "actually", "people", "in", "your", "country", "that", "decided", "long", "ago", "that", "they", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "have", "one", "man", "over", "an", "entire", "nation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Am I wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Let's get back to this issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "get", "back", "to", "this", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Let me ask you, do you know why there are no shootings on planes in America?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "do", "you", "know", "why", "there", "are", "no", "shootings", "on", "planes", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Because we have armed guards.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "have", "armed", "guards", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "understanding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "That is my understanding.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "my", "understanding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Wasn't that fun?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "that", "fun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "WDT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Firing weapons like that that are incredibly powerful, I've never really done it before.", "answer_tokens": ["Firing", "weapons", "like", "that", "that", "are", "incredibly", "powerful", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "really", "done", "it", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "If the answer isn't very convincing, why the least we couldn't do to those poor families who lost people to that weapon is not just remove those from the equation?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "answer", "is", "n't", "very", "convincing", ",", "why", "the", "least", "we", "could", "n't", "do", "to", "those", "poor", "families", "who", "lost", "people", "to", "that", "weapon", "is", "not", "just", "remove", "those", "from", "the", "equation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Well, a number of things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "number", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What don't I understand?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "n't", "I", "understand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "You don't understand that it's a simple inanimate tool that tens of millions of American families own, that have never caused a problem, never had an accident and will never commit a crime.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "understand", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "simple", "inanimate", "tool", "that", "tens", "of", "millions", "of", "American", "families", "own", ",", "that", "have", "never", "caused", "a", "problem", ",", "never", "had", "an", "accident", "and", "will", "never", "commit", "a", "crime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "It's not a minor aberration?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "minor", "aberration", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "You are so full of crap.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "so", "full", "of", "crap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "Do you care about murders or do you only care about murders with guns?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "care", "about", "murders", "or", "do", "you", "only", "care", "about", "murders", "with", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "I care about all death.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "care", "about", "all", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Which of his proposals do you agree with?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "of", "his", "proposals", "do", "you", "agree", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Well, I think I can frame it best by identifying the scammer in chief who claims that just to save one life would be worth this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "can", "frame", "it", "best", "by", "identifying", "the", "scammer", "in", "chief", "who", "claims", "that", "just", "to", "save", "one", "life", "would", "be", "worth", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "Isn't it worth it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "it", "worth", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "He had a chance to save four American lives in Benghazi and refused to do so.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "had", "a", "chance", "to", "save", "four", "American", "lives", "in", "Benghazi", "and", "refused", "to", "do", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "ORGAN: Do you agree with universal background checks?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "agree", "with", "universal", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Because the government doesn't need to know who has what.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "the", "government", "does", "n't", "need", "to", "know", "who", "has", "what", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "Do you think America is going to be safer because gun stores like this are selling so furiously and so much faster weapons and ammunition, increasing both in America?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "America", "is", "going", "to", "be", "safer", "because", "gun", "stores", "like", "this", "are", "selling", "so", "furiously", "and", "so", "much", "faster", "weapons", "and", "ammunition", ",", "increasing", "both", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Switzerland"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Do you know the two countries which have the highest per capita rate of firearms per civilian?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "two", "countries", "which", "have", "the", "highest", "per", "capita", "rate", "of", "firearms", "per", "civilian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "America and Switzerland, I believe.", "answer_tokens": ["America", "and", "Switzerland", ",", "I", "believe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "No, do you know what the second one is after America?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "do", "you", "know", "what", "the", "second", "one", "is", "after", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia", "Britain", "Japan", "Canada"]}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "A gun free zone in all these cities where the slaughter rate is the highest of anywhere, including Yemen?", "question_tokens": ["A", "gun", "free", "zone", "in", "all", "these", "cities", "where", "the", "slaughter", "rate", "is", "the", "highest", "of", "anywhere", ",", "including", "Yemen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "Let me give you some countries, Australia, Britain, Japan, Canada.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "give", "you", "some", "countries", ",", "Australia", ",", "Britain", ",", "Japan", ",", "Canada", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Yemen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 788, "question": "Are you sure of that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "sure", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "I wouldn't want you in a tank.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "want", "you", "in", "a", "tank", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]